さて…
Now, then...
いったい何をしてくれるんでしょうね
What on Earth are you going to do, hmm?
まずは三村が編集した動画を見て楽しんでもらって
First, you'll get to enjoy a video Mimura put together,
その後　テストで勝った７人が触手を破壊し
and then the seven top testers will destroy your tentacles.
それを合図にみんなで一斉に暗殺を始める
That'll be the signal for us all to jump in and begin the assassination.
Does that sound all right, Korosensei?
それでいいですよね　殺せんせー
上等です
More than all right.
セッティング　ご苦労さん　三村
Thanks for setting this up, Mimura.
頑張ったぜ
It was hard work! I was editing all through dinner.
みんなが飯食ってる間も　ずっと編集さ
このチャペルは周囲を海で囲まれている
This chapel is surrounded by ocean,
壁や窓には対先生物質が仕込まれている可能性もある
and there's a chance the walls and windows are treated with an anti-teacher substance.
脱出はリスクが高い
Escape would be too risky.
チャペルの中でよけきるしかないようですね
I suppose I'll just have to dodge everything in here.
殺せんせー
Korosensei?
まずはボディーチェックを
I have to pat you down first.
いくら周囲が水とはいえ
We may be surrounded by water, but if you smuggled in that swimsuit,
あの水着を隠し持ってたら逃げ切れるからね
you'd still be able to get away.
入念ですね
You're being so careful!
そんなやぼはしませんよ
But I wouldn't pull such a cheap trick.
これだけじかに触っている状態からでも
This teacher can easily dodge my attacks, even at point-blank range.
この先生は僕の攻撃など余裕でかわす
けど…
But...
みんなで　この作戦なら
If we all work together, this might be our chance!
kiritsu rei lock on
Stand, bow, lock on!
起立
礼
ロックオン
起立
kiritsu rei lock on
Stand, bow, lock on!
礼
ロックオン
oh yeah
Oh yeah!
sensei target on
The target is our teacher!
せんせー
ターゲットオン
总监.Maki
台本.小伍
ポテンシャル高い
总监.Maki
台本.小伍
potential takai
We've got a lot of potential
ポテンシャル高い
ほどめんどくさい
hodo mendokusai
It's just that we're not trying
ほどめんどくさい
总监.Maki
台本.小伍
ほどめんどくさい
ドロップアウト　メンタリティー
dropout mentality
We had that dropouts' mentality
ほどめんどくさい
ドロップアウト　メンタリティー
hinichijou wo ryougashi
No matter the unusual situation we were in
翻译.兰樱
非日常を凌駕し
校对.Maki
翻译.兰樱
非日常を凌駕し
校对.Maki
僕らはうたたね顔して
时间轴.歪歪
BDRip.VCB-Studio
bokura wa utatatanegao shite
We pretended to doze off
僕らはうたたね顔して
时间轴.歪歪
BDRip.VCB-Studio
僕らはうたたね顔して
knife kakushimotta
While holding on to a hidden knife
时间轴.歪歪
BDRip.VCB-Studio
僕らはうたたね顔して
时间轴.歪歪
BDRip.VCB-Studio
ナイフ隠し持った
起立
kiritsu rei lock on
Stand, bow, lock on
礼
ロックオン
hottokeba kitto dareka yatte kureru to
Thinking someone would deal with you eventually
ほっとけば　きっと誰か　やってくれると
どこか　他人事だった
doko ka taningoto datta
We didn't really feel invested in the job
どこか　他人事だった
だけど
dakedo
But now
だけど
mister teacher oshiete mikansei na bokura
Teacher, teach us, we're still growing up
Mr.ティーチャー教えて　未完成の僕ら
あなたという不落のターゲット　撃抜けるでしょうか
anata to iu furaku no target uchinukeru deshou ka
Will we be able to shoot through an invincible target like you?
あなたという不落のターゲット　撃抜けるでしょうか
idomu tabi ni kanousei ga afureta
kiritsu rei lock on
Our chances soar each time we challenge you
Stand, bow, lock on!
idomu tabi ni kanousei ga afureta
kiritsu rei lock on
挑む限り　可能性はハーフ＆ハーフ
Mr.ティーチャー見ていて　迷い多き僕ら
mister teacher mite ite mayoi ooki bokura
Teacher, watch us, as we try to find a direction in life
Mr.ティーチャー見ていて　迷い多き僕ら
誰よりもあなたのために猛勉強中さ
dare yori mo anata no tame ni moubenkyouchuu sa
We're studying our ass off for you more than anybody else
誰よりもあなたのために猛勉強中さ
殺意だけが　あなたへのメッセージ
satsui dake ga anata e no message
Only the bloodlust is our message to you
kiritsu rei lock on
Stand, bow, lock on!
殺意だけが　あなたへのメッセージ
自力　ガチで
jiriki gachi de hongan iku yo
We'll make our dreams come true on our own for real
自力　ガチで
本願　行くよ
revolution
A revolution!
レボリューション
oh yeah
Oh yeah!
せんせー
sensei target on
The target is our teacher!
せんせー
ターゲットオン
Episode
Action
Time
本字幕由诸神字幕组出品，仅供学习交流，禁止用于商业用途
更多中日双语字幕，尽在 i.kamigami.org 及微博 @诸神字幕组
準備はいいですか
Are you ready?
遠慮は無用　どんと来なさい
No need to hold back.
Come right at me!
始めるぜ　殺せんせー
Here we go, Korosensei.
AC...
「東京都内某所　椚ヶ丘中学　３年Ｅ組」
Somewhere in Tokyo: Kunugigaoka Junior High, Class 3-E.
「あろうことか　この学級の担任教師は暗殺のターゲットである」
As it happens, their teacher is also their assassination target.
後ろの暗がりで　チャペルを出入りしている
People are going in and out of this chapel in the dark behind me.
Tonight, the E Class recon team will close in
位置と人数を明確にしないためでしょう
That would conceal the number of people and their positions.
on the ecology of this mystery man.
しかし　甘い
But you underestimate me.
２人のにおいがここにないのを分かってますよ
I can tell two students' scents are missing.
そちらの方向から
From that direction, I can smell the E Class's top snipers, Hayami-san and Chiba-kun.
Ｅ組きってのスナイパー　速水さんと千葉君のにおいがしてきますねぇ
This video really is well done.
しかし　この動画よくできている
編集とナレーターが三村君ですか
You edited and narrated this, Mimura-kun?
カット割りといい選曲といい　いいセンス
Nice camera blocking, good music... Really sharp.
ついつい　引き込まれ…
It pulls me right—
Joining us today are those who shared top-secret intel with the recon team.
我々調査隊に極秘情報を提供してくださった方々にお越しいただきました
Today's Target: Korosensei
お話を伺う前に　続きをご覧ください
We'll hear what they have to say... after this.
「買収は
His bribery... failed.
Tokyo resident
Korosensei
(age unknown)
Tokyo resident
Korosensei
(age unknown)
失敗した」
It failed?!
失敗したぁぁー
His current preference is mature office women.
「最近のマイブームは熟女ＯＬ」
Here are all the dirty magazines this octopus has gathered.
「全てこのタコが一人で集めたエロ本である」
えっ　そう…　違う　ちょっ…
No! Come on, Okajima-kun!
岡島くんたち　みんなに言うなとあれほど
I told you guys not to tell anyone!
「女子限定のケーキバイキングに並ぶ巨影」
A giant shadow looms over the line for the women-only cake buffet.
「誰あろう」
Who could it be?
It's him.
「やつである」
殺子よ
I'm Koroko!
Excuse me, but this is for women only...
His disguise can't last long.
「バレないはずがない」
お客様　申し訳ございません…
What do you think you're doing?!
「女装以前に人間じゃないとバレなかっただけ　奇跡である」
It's a miracle they found out he wasn't a woman without discovering he wasn't even human.
Porn, cross-dressing, and not a hint of shame?
エロ本に女装に　恥ずかしくないの　ど変態
What a dirty pervert.
Take one!
When he's short before payday,
「給料前」
お願いしま～す
Thanks!
this man lines up his images to get free tissues.
どうも
「男は分身でティッシュ配りの行列に並ぶ」
Thanks!
「そんなに取って　どうするのかと思いきや…」
And what does he do with them?
Thanks!
「空揚げにして食べだした」
Fries them up and eats them.
今日はポケットティッシュの空揚げ
Here we have fried pocket tissues!
先生　この間気づいたんです　ティッシュって意外と甘いんですよ
I recently noticed they have quite a sweet taste to them,
「教師…　いや　生物としての尊厳はあるのだろうか」
Has he no dignity as an educator—nay, as a living being?
皆さん　ご存知の通り…
and a pleasant spongy texture.
And that's not all.
「こんなものでは終わらない」
「この教師の恥ずかしい映像を　１時間たっぷりとお見せしよう」
We have a full hour of embarrassing footage of this instructor.
Another hour of this?!
あと１時間も
One Hour Later
死んだ…　もう先生死にました…
I'm dead. I'm already dead.
あんなの知られて　もう生きていけません…
With all that out in the open... I can't go on living.
The End
「さて　極秘映像にお付き合いいただいたが
Now, did you happen to notice anything while you sat through our top-secret video,
The End
何かお気付きではないだろうか　殺せんせー」
Korosensei?
The End
Water!
水が
But I didn't sense anyone pouring it in!
誰も水など流す気配はなかったのに…
まさか…
It couldn't be...
満潮
High tide!
誰かが小屋の支柱を短くでもしたんだろう
Someone musta shortened the support pilings on this here chapel.
Seasick, shamed, and now waterlogged...
船に酔って　恥ずかしい思いして　海水吸って
You've slowed down quite a bit.
だいぶ動きが鈍ってきたよね
さあ　本番だ
Now for the main event...
約束だ　よけんなよ
A promise is a promise. No dodgin', now.
やりますね…
A valiant effort. But I know where the snipers are.
しかし　スナイパーのいる方向は分かっている
If I just keep an eye out in that direction...
そちらの方向さえ注意すれば…
作戦開始
Commence operation!
Begin!
開始
Five seconds elapsed.
５秒経過
Did it come apart?!
壊れた
Yes!
やったー
Thirty-five seconds elapsed.
３５秒経過
フライボード
Flyboards?
水圧のおり
A hydraulic cage?!
Korosensei doesn't do well with sudden changes to his environment.
殺せんせーは急激な環境の変化に弱い
From the chapel to a cage of water!
チャペルから水のおりへ
It'll confuse his weakened tentacles
弱った触手を混乱させて　反応速度をさらに落とす
and lower his reaction speed even further!
Fifty-three seconds elapsed.
５３秒経過
Commencing volley.
一斉射撃を開始します
Taking aim.
照準　殺せんせーの周囲を全周１ｍ
Target area: one square meter around Korosensei.
Korosensei is highly sensitive to attacks that make contact.
殺せんせーは当たる攻撃に敏感だ
だから　あえて先生を狙わない
But we're actually not going to aim at him!
We'll block his escape path with a hail of bullets!
弾幕を張り　逃げ道をふさぐ
And that's not all!
か～ら～の
The final blow...
とどめの　２人
goes to those two!
The ones onshore are two dummies infused with their scents!
陸の上のは２人のにおいが染み込んだダミー
By alerting him to the shore while in the chapel
室内で陸上を警戒させておき
フィールドを水のおりへ変えることで
and changing the setting to a water cage,
まったく別の狙撃点をつくり出す
we've created a whole new sniping target!
Game over!
ゲームオーバーです
You've done well... to come this far!
よくぞ　ここまで…
渚
Nagisa!
This is clearly unlike any of our previous attempts—
今までの暗殺とは明らかに違う
it feels like it worked!
やった手応え…
Stay alert!
油断するな
He can regenerate!
やつには再生能力がある
Isogai-kun, Kataoka-san, you're in charge of watching the water!
磯貝君　片岡さんが中心になって　水面を見張れ
Yes, sir!
はい
But he had nowhere to run!
逃げ場はどこにもなかったはず
Look!
あれ
Hey...
おい…
Uh-huh...
What the hell is that?
何あれ…
My trump card of all trump cards: my absolute defense form!
これぞ　先生の奥の手中の奥の手　完全防御形態
Absolute defense form?!
完全防御形態
Absolute Defense Form?!
The exterior is crystallized,
high-density condensed energy.
外側の部分は高密度に凝縮されたエネルギーの結晶体です
The energy remaining after shrinking my body down hardens in a shell around it.
肉体を思い切り小さく縮め
その分　余分になったエネルギーで肉体の周囲をがっちり固める
In this form, I'm absolutely invincible!
この形態になった先生はまさに無敵
No way...
そんな…
So if you always stay in that form, we can never kill you!
じゃあ　ずっとその形態でいたら殺せないじゃん
ところが　そううまくはいきません
If only that were the case.
Absolute Defense Form
High-Density Energy Crystal
Core
This energy crystal will break down in about a day.
このエネルギー結晶は約１日で自然崩壊します
Absolute Defense Form
High-Density Energy Crystal
Core
Absolute Defense Form
High-Density Energy Crystal
Core
Absolute Defense Form
High-Density Energy Crystal
Core
Absolute Defense Form
High-Density Energy Crystal
Core
Breakdown Begins
After 24 Hours
Physical Regeneration
During Reconstruction
Breakdown Begins
After 24 Hours
Physical Regeneration
During Reconstruction
And the moment it does, my body will re-inflate,
その瞬間に　先生は肉体を膨らませ
Physical Regeneration
During Reconstruction
Complete
Recovery
エネルギーを吸収して　元の体に戻るわけです
absorbing energy and returning to its usual form.
Complete
Recovery
On the other hand, for the one day or so until this crystal decays,
裏を返せば　結晶が崩壊するまでの約１日
先生はまったく身動きがとれません
I can't move an inch.
This brings with it certain risks.
これは様々なリスクを伴います
What happened to the thing I left here?!
ここにあったやつは
燃えるごみに出しといたよ
I put it out with the trash.
Burnables
オーノー
Oh, nooo!
What I'm most afraid of is being placed into a high-speed rocket during that time
最も恐れるのは　その間に高速ロケットに詰め込まれ
and left to float through the far reaches of outer space.
はるか遠くの宇宙空間に捨てられることですが…
But I've thoroughly studied that eventuality.
その点は　抜かりなく調べ済みです
Nowhere in the world is there a rocket capable of making that flight within 24 hours.
２４時間以内にそれが可能なロケットは　今世界のどこにもない
He got us.
やられた…
Another trick up his sleeve—after all that.
ここにきての隠し技
And he even took its weak points into account!
その欠点まで　ちゃんと計算ずくで…
That was an utter failure.
完敗だ
Invincible, my ass.
何が無敵だよ
Somethin' like this has gotta be breakable somehow!
何とかすりゃ壊せんだろ　こんなもん
無駄ですね　核爆弾でも傷一つつきませんよ
It's no use. Even a nuclear bomb wouldn't leave a scratch.
Oh, I get it.
そっか
No weaknesses means we're out of options.
弱点ないんじゃ打つ手ないね
No! Stop! I can't cover my face without any hands!
やめて　手がないから　顔も覆えないんです
ごめん　ごめ～ん　じゃあ　取りあえず…
Sorry, sorry! Then I'll just...
stick this sea slug on you!
そこで拾ったウミウシ　引っ付けとくね
キモっ
Someone go find me a filthy old guy so I can jam this thing down his underpants!
超キモい
あと　誰か不潔なおっさん見つけてきて
これ　パンツの中にねじ込むから
No! Help!
やめて　助けて
ある意味　いじり放題だよね
When you think about it, we can do whatever we want with him.
Yep. And this kind of thing is Karma-kun's specialty.
うん…　そして　こういうときの業君は天才的だ
We'll disperse for now, students.
取りあえず解散だ　みんな
The top brass and I will discuss how to deal with this one.
上層部とこいつの処分法を検討する
Going to throw me in a pool full of anti-teacher material?
対先生物質のプールの中にでも封じ込めますか
It won't work.
無駄ですよ
I can simply make a portion of my energy explode,
その場合は　エネルギーの一部を爆発させて
creating a blast like before that'd send things flying.
さっきのように　爆風で周囲を吹き飛ばしてしまいますから
But you should be proud.
ですが　君たちは誇ってよい
世界中の軍隊でも　先生をここまで追い込めなかった
Even the world's combined military couldn't get this far with me.
It all comes down to the magnificence of your plan.
ひとえに　皆さんの計画の素晴らしさです
Korosensei praised our assassination like he always does,
殺せんせーはいつものように僕らの暗殺を褒めてくれたけど
but it was our biggest disappointment yet.
かつてなく大掛かりな全員での渾身の一撃を外したショック
Still in shock from our all-in, full-throttle attack missing the mark,
coupled with an unusual sense of fatigue,
異常な疲労感とともに　僕らはホテルへの帰途に就いた
we made our way back to the hotel.
Ritsu?
律
はい
Yes?
You recorded that, right?
記録はとれてたろ
Yes! I captured as much of the assassination as possible with my high-speed camera.
はい　可能なかぎり　ハイスピード撮影で今回の暗殺の一部始終を
I knew the second I fired that I'd missed.
俺さ　撃った瞬間　分かっちゃったよ
That my bullet couldn't kill him.
ミスった
この弾じゃ殺せないって
I can't say for sure.
断定はできません
The exact time it took him to change into that form is unclear.
あの形態に移行するまでの正確な時間は不明瞭なので
However, if your shot had been 0.5 seconds faster,
ですが　千葉君の射撃があと０．５秒速いか
or if Hayami-san's had been thirty centimeters closer,
速水さんの射撃があと３０ｃｍ近ければ
you would have had a fifty percent chance of killing him before he noticed.
気付く前に殺せた可能性が５０％ほど存在します
I was so confident. I mean, we rehearsed
自信はあったんだ
リハーサルはもちろん
and even practiced firing from a less stable spot—and I didn't miss.
あそこより不安定な場所で練習しても外さなかった
だけど　いざあの瞬間
But when the time came, my fingers stiffened and my vision narrowed.
指先が硬直して視界が狭まった
Same here.
同じく
The pressure of absolutely not being allowed to miss...
絶対に外せないというプレッシャー
That crucial now-or-never moment...
ここしかないって大事な瞬間
To think it'd be this different from practice.
こんなにも練習と違うとはね
しっかし　疲れたわ
I'm just so exhausted!
Let's head back to our room and rest.
部屋戻って休もうか
I don't feel like doing anything.
もう何もする気ねえ
What, one lousy miss and you lose all your energy?
んだよ　てめえら　１回外したぐらいでだれやがって
We did what we were supposed to do,
so tomorrow we can just enjoy ourselves!
もうやることやったんだから
あした一日　遊べんだろうが
Ooh, yeah! Tomorrow I get to take in some swimsuited beauties for sure!
そうそう　あしたこそ水着ギャルをじっくり見んだ
どんなに疲れてても　全力で鼻血出すぜ
No matter how tired I may be, I'll always have the energy for a hearty nosebleed!
そんな元気ねえよ…
Man, I'm just not feeling it.
水着ギャルでボン　水着ギャルでボン
Something isn't right. Everyone's too exhausted!
何か変だ…
いくら何でも　みんな　疲れ過ぎじゃ…
Can I lean on you for a second, Nagisa-kun?
渚君よう　肩貸しちゃくれんかね…
Nakamura-san!
中村さん
I want to go back to the room and change,
部屋に戻ってとっとと着替えたいんだけどさ
but I can't seem to move my body at all.
ちっとも体が動かんのよ…
You're burning up!
ひどい熱
いや　もう想像しただけで鼻血…
Just imagining those babes is giving me a nosebleed!
岡島君
Okajima-kun!
Wh-What the...
こっ　これは…
Hey! Where's the hospital on this island?
君　この島の病院はどこだ
Well... I'm afraid the island is too small to have one.
いや　なにぶん小さな島なので
Incoming Call
Private Number
Hey there, Sensei.
やあ　先生　カワイイ生徒がずいぶん苦しそうだね
Your precious students seem to be in a real bad way.
Who is this?!
何者だ
Hey, Ritsu!
ねえ　律
Who I am doesn't matter.
俺が誰か何者かなど　どうでもいい
Those brats aren't the only ones going after that marked man.
賞金首を狙っているのはがきどもだけじゃないってことさ
You mean you did this?
まさか　これはお前の仕業か
How observant.
察しがいい
It's an artificial virus.
人工的に作り出したウイルスだ
Playing Audio
Once you're infected, it's all over.
一度感染したら最後　潜伏期間や初期症状に個人差はあれ
The incubation period and initial symptoms vary,
１週間もすれば　全身の細胞がぐずぐずになって死に至る
but the cells in their bodies will break down within a week,
leading to death.
There's only one remedy, also an original concoction,
治療薬も一種のみのオリジナルでね
but unfortunately, I'm the only one who has it.
あいにく　こちらにしか手持ちがない
I can't be bothered bringing it to you, so you'd better come get it directly.
渡すのが面倒だから　直接取りに来てくれないか
There's a hotel atop this island's mountain.
この島の山頂にホテルがある
Bring me the one with the price on his head.
手土産はそこの賞金首だ
Come up to the top floor within one hour.
今から１時間以内で最上階まで持ってこい
However, Sensei, you seem pretty tough yourself. Dangerous, even.
だが　先生よ　お前は腕が立つそうだから危険だな
So send your two shortest students still standing—one boy, one girl.
そうだ　動ける生徒の中で
最も背が低い男女２人に持ってこさせろ
I've told the front desk to expect you.
こちらのフロントには話を通してある
Follow the rules, and we'll swap the target for the remedy and that'll be that.
普通に来れば　賞金首と薬の交換はすぐに済む
だが　外部と連絡を取ったり　少しでも遅れれば
But contact any outsider, or be even a little late, and the remedy...
即座に治療薬は
will be history.
破壊する
礼を言うよ　よくぞそいつを行動不能まで追い込んでくれた
I've got to thank you for immobilizing him like that.
Looks like the gods are on our side.
天はわれわれの味方のようだ
Private Number
Call Ended
End
A third party joining the fray at a time like this? Unbelievable!
まさか…　こんなときに第三者が狙ってくるとは
Uh, Karasuma-sensei, aren't you being a little rough? Er...
Karasuma-san?
烏間さん　案の定　駄目です
As we expected, it's no use.
政府として　あのホテルに問い合わせても
Even when we play the government card,
プライバシーの保護を繰り返すばかりで
the hotel just responds with claims of privacy protection.
やはりか
It figures.
Does it?
やはり
That mountaintop hotel is a noted site for illegal negotiation.
あの山頂のホテルは政府からもマークされている違法な商談場所らしくてな
A remote island in the southern sea?
南海の孤島ってロケーションが　おあつらえ向きってことね
Couldn't ask for a better location.
政府のお偉いさんともパイプがあり　うかつに警察も手が出せん
They have connections with some government higher-ups.
Even the police have their hands tied.
Clearly they're not going to cooperate with us.
そんなホテルがこっちに味方するわけないね
What are we gonna do? At this rate, it'll be a massacre!
どうすんすか　このままじゃ　いっぱい死んじまう
こ…殺されるために　この島来たんじゃねえよ
We didn't come here to be killed!
Calm down, Yoshida-kun. We won't die that easily.
落ち着いて　吉田君
そんな簡単に死なない　死なない
Just come up with a way to deal with this.
じっくり　対策　考えてよ
Yeah... Sorry, Hara.
悪ぃな　原
It's too dicey to do what he says.
言うこと聞くのも危険過ぎんぜ
Send your two runtiest students?
一番チビの２人で来いだ
このちんちくりんどもだぞ
These two squirts?!
人質増やすようなもんだろ
We'd just be handin' him hostages!
第一よ　こんなやり方するやつらにムカついてしょうがねえ
First off, I'm pissed at anyone who would even do this kinda thing.
人の連れにまで手出しやがって
No one lays a finger on my flunkies!
That simple-minded guy...
単細胞が…
Heh heh...
要求なんざ全シカトだ
I say we ignore his demands!
Let's get everyone to a hospital in the city!
今すぐ全員都会の病院に運んで…
I'm against that.
賛成しないな
If it really is an unknown artificial virus,
もし本当に人工的に作った未知のウイルスなら
even the biggest hospitals won't have the antivirals to stop it.
対応できる抗ウイルス薬はどんな大病院にも置いていない
The time wasted in bringing in the sick could hurt them more.
いざ運んで無駄足になれば　患者のリスクを増やすだけだ
Say what?!
んだと
We'll work on treating the symptoms for now.
対症療法で応急処置はしとくから
You'd better hurry to the trade-off spot.
急いで取引に行った方がいい
Takebayashi...
竹林…
There's nothing else we can do.
打つ手なしだ
If Korosensei could move, we might've had a chance.
殺せんせーが動けるなら　手の打ちようもあるのに…
If only our assassination attempt hadn't gone quite so well for nothing.
僕らの暗殺が下手にいいところまでいったせいで…
敵の目的はこいつだが…
So he's the one they're after.
I'm not sure that guy will just let the students go after they deliver him.
渡しに行った生徒を素直にかえしてくれるかしら
What should we do? We only have one hour.
どうする…　リミットは１時間
There's still a way.
いい方法がありますよ
Korosensei?
殺せんせー
All set!
ＯＫです
It looks like Ritsu-san's completed the prep work I asked her to do.
律さんに頼んでおいた下調べも終わったようです
I need the healthy students to come here.
元気な人は来てください
Wear something you don't mind getting dirty.
汚れてもいい格好でね
It's so high...
高え…
I infiltrated the hotel's computers
あのホテルのコンピューターに侵入して
and got schematics of the interior, complete with guard locations.
内部の図面を入手しました
警備の配置図も
A large number of guards are stationed at and around the main entrance.
正面玄関と敷地一帯には大量の警備が置かれています
フロントを通らずにホテルに入るのは　まず不可能
It's not possible to enter the hotel without going past the front desk.
With one exception: there is an entryway on this side, atop the ledge.
しかし　ただ一つ　こちら側の崖を登った所に出入り口があります
The terrain is impassable,
まず侵入不可能な地形故　警備も配置されていないようです
and there are no guards posted there.
If you don't want the enemy to get his way...
敵の意のままになりたくないなら
手段は一つ
there's only one thing to do!
Not counting the ten patients and the two left behind to care for them,
患者１０人と看病に残してきた２人を除き
all capable students must sneak in from here,
動ける生徒全員でここから侵入
get the jump on the guys at the top,
最上階を奇襲して　治療薬を奪い取るのです
and steal that remedy!
太陽が射す　閉ざした瞼の裏側に赤い残像
The sun shines
taiyou ga sasu
On the back of my closed eyelids
tozashita mabuta no uragawa ni
I see red afterimages
akai zanzou
With a notebook and a pen in my leather bag
kawa no kaban ni nooto to pen wo
革の鞄に　ノートとペンを　さあ歩き出そう
I go for a walk
saa arukidasou
I keep drawing, but I can't get it to look pretty
kaitemo kaitemo kirei ni naranai
描いても描いても　綺麗にならない
My choice of colors is not to blame
eranda enogu ni tsumi wa nai
選んだ絵の具に　罪はない
I still remember the shooting star I saw last night
kinou no yonaka ni mita nagareboshi mada oboeteiru
昨日の夜中に見た流れ星　まだ覚えている
I was waiting for...
I was waiting for…
Hello shooting-star Hello shooting-star again
Hello, shooting star
Hello, shooting star, again
I was waiting
matteita yo
待っていたよ
夢を見るあの子はずっと
The girl of many dreams
yume wo miru ano ko wa zutto
ここにいるの　Ah　Ah
Is always here
koko ni iru no
あの日のまま　Ah　Ah
Just like you did that day
ano hi no mama
また光って
Shine again
mata hikatte
Irina Jelavich's...
イリーナ・イェラビッチの
Irina Jelavich's
Super-Secret Skills Series!
超絶秘術シリーズ
Super-Secret Skills Series
Irina-sensei can control her circulation
イリーナ先生は体の血流を操作して顔色を自在に変える
ｕｓｕａｌｌｙ
Normal.
to change her face color at will.
Red makes her look shy or drunk,
赤は照れや酔い
Red.
ｒｅｄ
and blue makes her look uneasy or unwell:
青は不安や体調不良を装うことができ
Blue.
ｂｌｕｅ
潜入の時には絶大な効果を発揮する
an extremely effective tactic when going undercover.
生徒に自慢しようと見せたが
When she tried to show this off to her students,
Look at this!
they accused her of being a cheap Korosensei ripoff.
殺せんせーの劣化パクリと言われ
I can change the color of my face!
素で赤くなって怒ってしまいました
She got angry, and her face went all red by itself.
I didn't rip off anyone!
パクってねえし
Assassination Classroom!
暗殺教室
Irina Jelavich's...
イリーナ・イェラビッチの
Irina Jelavich's
Super-Secret Skills Series!
超絶秘術シリーズ
Super-Secret Skills Series
Irina-sensei can pop out the parts of a cereal-box prize and assemble it within one minute.
イリーナ先生は　食玩程度なら
Fast Forward
パーツを切り離し　組み立てまでを１分でできる
彼女のキステクを物語る絶技だが
Fast Forward
While this speaks volumes about her kissing techniques,
正直　あんまり触りたくないですね
we still wouldn't want to touch the finished product.
Also: this is dangerous, kids, so don't try it at home.
Rewind
あと　危ないから　まねしちゃ駄目
Assassination Classroom.
暗殺教室
Irina Jelavich's...
イリーナ・イェラビッチの
Irina Jelavich's
Super-Secret Skills Series!
超絶秘術シリーズ
Super-Secret Skills Series
Irina-sensei can use her wig know-how to disguise herself as any number of people.
イリーナ先生は　ウィッグテクによって
様々な人物に変装することができるのである
だってばよ
Believe it!
犯人はお前だ
The culprit is... you!
奥田さん
ウイルスは遺伝子を持ち　増殖するという生物に似た特徴を持っていますが
生物の基本である細胞という構造を持っていません
生物から余分なものを徹底的に取り除いた
一種の究極進化形態と見なせないこともないですね
次回　暗殺教室　伏魔の時間